Guide to the Gathering of the Tribes Archive 1983-2006 MSS.198
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series IV: Grant Applications
  - Puffin Foundation, 1996-1997 (Box 19, Folder 71)
  - Puffin Foundation Fiscal Year '01, 1999-2000 (Box 19, Folder 72)
  - Puffin Foundation, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 73)
  - Puffin Foundation, Fiscal Year '00 Request, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 74)
  - Puffin Foundation (12/01) Grant Application, Decmber 2001 (Box 19, Folder 75)
  - Workshop Contract, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 76)
  - WTC Business Recovery Grant Program, 2002 (Box 19, Folder 77)
- Series V: Financial Records
  Materials are arranged and described alphabetically by file title.
  - Budgets, 2000 (Actual) - 2003 (Projected) (Box 19, Folder 78)
  - Check Ledgers, 2001-2002 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Check Ledgers, 2002 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Check Ledgers, 2002-2003 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Check Ledgers, 2002 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Check Ledgers, 2002 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Check Ledgers, 2002 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Checking Account Statements, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 79)
  - Checking Account Statements (1 of 2), 2000-2005 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Checking Account Statements (2 of 2), 2000-2005 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Checking Account Statements, 2001 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Checking Account Statements, 2001 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Checking Account Statements, 2001 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Checking Account Statements, 2002-2003 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Checking Account Statements, 2002-2003 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Checks, 1998 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Checks, 1998 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Checks, 1998 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Checks, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Checks, 2002 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Checks, 2002 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Checks, 2002 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Checks, 2003 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Online Magazine Budget, 2005 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Receipts, 2000-2002 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Tax / Account Stuff, 1998 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Tax / Account Stuff (1 of 3), 1999 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Tax / Account Stuff (2 of 3), 1999 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Tax / Account Stuff (3 of 3), 1999 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Tax / Account Stuff, 2000 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Tax / Account Stuff, 2001 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Tax Returns, 2000 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - Tax Returns, 2001 (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - Tax Returns, 2002 (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - Tax Returns, 2003 (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - Tribes Bills, 1998 (Box 20, Folder 28)
  - Tribes Bills, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 29)
  - Tribes Bills, 2000 (Box 20, Folder 30)
- Series VI: Publications
  Items are arranged alphabetically by author/editor.
  - Axel, Brett. First on the Fire. New York: Fly By Night, 1999. (Box 20, Folder 31)
  - Benson, Tish. Wild Like That: Good Stuff Smellin Strong. New York: Fly By Night, 2003 (Box 20, Folder 32)
    Introduction by Sapphire.
  - Boadiba. Under Burning White Sky. Berkeley, CA: Ishmael Reed Publising Company, 2005. (Box 20, Folder 33)
  - Carter, Michael. Broken Noses and Metempsychoses. New York: Fly By Night, 1996. (Box 20, Folder 34)
  - Freedman, Katherine Rose. Straight to the Point. Westport, CT: RozyPozy Press, 2005. (Box 20, Folder 35)
  - Kim, Anyssa. Ovarian Twists: New and Selected Poems. New York: Fly By Night, 2003. (Box 20, Folder 36)
  - Mozon, Nadine. Kiss it Up to God. New York: Fly By Night, 2001. (Box 20, Folder 37)
  - Murphy, Jennifer. Remain. New York: Fly By Night, 2005. (Box 20, Folder 38)
  - Ouzoonian, Amy, ed. In the Arms of Words: Poems for Disaster Relief. Santa Fe: Sherman Asher, 2006. (Box 20, Folder 39)
  - Ouzoonian, Amy, ed. Skyscrapers, Taxis and Tampons. New York: Fly By Night, 1999. (Box 20, Folder 40)
  - Packer, Eve. Skulls Head Samba. New York: Fly By Night, 1993. (Box 20, Folder 41)
  - Purcell, Barbara. Black Ice. New York: Fly By Night, 2006. (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Rux, Carl Hancock. Pagan Operetta. New York: Fly By Night, 1999. (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Semerdjian, Alan. An Improvised Device. Lock n' Load Press, 2005. (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Taylor, Cheryl Boyce. Raw Air. New York: Fly By Night, 1997. (Box 21, Folder 11)
- Series VII: Data Storage
  Items were given unique IDs and described at the item level.
  Born-digital materials have not been preserved and may not be available to researchers.
  - Tribes Gallery Show, March 2001; 1 media elements; Original Format: Iomega Zip PC100; Label annotation: "Photo: Delano Franklin" (Box 9, Disk ID: 198.3.0001)
  - Tribes Books, 2002; 1 media elements; Original Format: CD-R (Box 9, Disk ID: 198.3.0002)
  - Wynton Marsalis Story, 2002-2003; 1 media elements; Original Format: 3 1/2 in. floppy disk. (Box 9, Disk ID: 198.3.0003)
- OVERSIZE Series III: Project Files
  - Articles, 2000 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - A Gathering of the Tribes Jacket Designs, 1993-1998 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Photograph: Steve Cannon and Stoop Writers Group Upstairs at Tribes Gallery, February 1995 (Map-case 4.A, Folder 1)
  - Photographs, 1995, undated (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Posters, 1996-2004 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Posters, 2004-05, undated (Box 22, Folder 5)